Littauer Library Collection of Miscellaneous Union Files 5964
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Agreements - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1940's-1970. (Box 31)
  - 2 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1952-1964 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - 3 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1955-1964 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - 4 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1956-1964 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - 5 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1958-1962 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Agreements - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1940's-1970. Also includes: (Box 32)
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1960 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Local 526, Pamphlets and Agreements, 1953-1970 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Misc. pamphlets and papers
  - 1 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1962-1970 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 2 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1961-1970 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - 3 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1953-1970 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - 4 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1960-1970 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - 5 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1960-1969 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 6 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1958-1970 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - 7 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1960-1970 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - 8 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1955-1970 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - 9 Agreement Files, Local 526, 1957-1967 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- 13 1936 Rank and File Leaflets - Fragile Originals (Box 33, Folder 1)
  Original leaflets
- 31 1941 Convention, Cleveland - Fragile Originals (Box 33, Folder 2)
  Original documents
- History of Marine Transportation - Fragile Originals (Box 33, Folder 3)
- 47 Lease - Lend, Fragile Originals, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- 49 NMU and War - Fragile Originals, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  Original pamphlets and papers
- 48 Pan American Seaman's Organization - Fragile Originals, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- 162 Seamen and Spain (fragile originals), 1937 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- 70 Precious Documents - Fragile Originals, 1935-1937 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  Original booklets
- 70 Precious Documents - Fragile Originals continued, 1937-1940 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- 61 NMU and World War II - fragile originals, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Joseph Curran Addresses - Fragile Originals, 1939-1940 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- 159 Seamen in the War - Fragile Originals, 1940-1944 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- 57 NMU and Discrimination - Fragile Originals, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- 60 Curran Anti War - peace speeches - fragile originals, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- 63 Shipping Scandals in World War II - fragile originals, 1941-1946 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- 77 Historical - Fragile Originals, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  Magazine and original documents
- 69 NMU Post War - fragile originals, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- 65 Standard, W - British Influence in U.S. Merchant Marine - Fragile Originals, 1941 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  Original document
- 79 Ship owner Profit - Fragile Originals, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- 101 Curran Reports to National Council - Fragile Originals, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- 103 Nazi Cells - Fragile Originals, 1940 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- 105 Curran Profile - Boyer - Fragile Originals, 1946 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- 112 Ship Owner Conniving and Federal Funds - Depredations - Fragile Originals, 1936 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  Original documents and booklets
- 113 Lewis Article for Journal of Commerce - Fragile Original (Box 33, Folder 24)
- 116 National Council - Fragile Originals, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- 167 ARTA Disruption - Fragile Originals, 1939 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- 165 Letter to Hull, July of 1937 - Fragile Originals (Box 33, Folder 27)
  Original letter
- 164 Filipino Issue - Fragile Originals (Box 33, Folder 28)
- 119 Scandinavian Seamen - Fragile Originals, 1938 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- 126 NMU Organizational Chart - Fragile Originals (Box 33, Folder 30)
  Original chart
- Constitutions NMU 1937 - Fragile Originals (Box 33, Folder 31)
- 3 WRC Bulletin - Assorted Issues (Waterfront Research Committee) 1938, 1939, 1940 - Fragile Originals, 1938-1940 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- 20 "Hours, wages, and working conditions in Domestic Water Transportation" Vol II (Fragile Originals), 1936 (Box 33, Folder 33)
- 20 "Hours, wages, and working conditions in Domestic Water Transportation" Vol I (Fragile Originals), 1936 (Box 33, Folder 34)
- 53 Fall 1936 Strike Minutes (Fragile Originals), 1936-1937 (Box 33, Folder 35)
- 107 Wages and Working Conditions - Fragile Originals, 1936-1939 (Box 33, Folder 36)
- 89 Resolution Terminating Fall Strike (Fragile Originals), 1937 (Box 33, Folder 37)
- 6 Affidavit of Rank and File Against ISU Leadership, 1936 - Fragile Originals (Box 33, Folder 38)
- 100 Seamen's Journal Fragile Originals, 1936 (Box 33, Folder 39)
- War Risk Insurance and Compensation - Fragile Originals, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- 110 Bureau of Marine Inspections and Navigation - C.D. Mallory, Fragile Originals, 1937-1940 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- 152 Bureau of Marine Inspection and Navigation Hearing - Fragile Originals, 1934 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- 90 Tanker Strike - Fragile Originals, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- 30 Tanker Strike - Late Thirties, Fragile Originals, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- 30 Tanker Strike - Late Thirties, Fragile Original Continued, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- 85 Dirksen Bill - Exhibits List and Memo Draft and Outline, Fragile Originals (Box 34, Folder 7)
- 15 Briefs of William L. Standard, Lifting of Seamen's Certificates for Union Activity - Fragile Originals, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- 4 Curran Testimony, Dirksen Bill (HR 2662 1939) - Fragile Originals (Box 34, Folder 9)
- 76 Other Legislation, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Answering Legislative Attacks - Fragile Originals, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- 56 Unity Movements East and West Coast - Fragile Originals, 1937-1939 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- 84 Unity Leaflet, 1937-1938 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  Misc. papers and leaflets
- West Coast Pamphlets, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  Misc. papers and pamphlets
- 15 William L. Standard - Fragile Originals, 1938-1941 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- 19 Marine Cooks and Stewards - Fragile Originals, 1936-1938 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- 117 West Coast - Fragile Originals, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- 80 Owens Affidavits (MFOW Frauds) - Fragile Originals, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- 125 Harry Bridges - Fragile Originals, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- 121 King-Conner-Ramsey, Fragile Originals, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- 120 SUP (Sailors' Union of the Pacific) - Fragile Originals, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- 109 Ferguson Case - Fragile Originals, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Bridges Hearing, San Francisco 3 January 1942 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Bridges Trials etc. (Fragile Originals), 1941 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- 122 West Coast Strike 1936, 1937 - Fragile Originals (Box 34, Folder 25)
- 161 Misc. Leaflets - Fragile Originals, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Current Anti-Labor Activities - D.J. Saposs (Fragile Originals), 1938 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- 100 Fragile Originals, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Early Leaflets - Fragile Originals, 1934-1937 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- 71 Howard Cullman Reports, "Safety at Sea" Agitation (Fragile Originals), 1935-1936 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- "Safety at Sea" Addresses (Fragile Originals), 1936 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- 68 NRA Code Hearings - Fragile Originals, 1933-1938 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Last Folder - Fragile Originals, 1938-1939 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- 8 Paddy Whalen Case (Patrick) - Fragile Originals, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- NMU Post War - Fragile Originals, 1945 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Racketeering in Merchant Marine - Fragile Originals, 1916-1937 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- International Merchant Marine Control and Destruction of U.S. Lines - Fragile Originals (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Outline - Mail Subsidies, Black Committee Merchant Marine Act 1932 - Fragile Originals (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - Boston Branch, NMU - Fragile Originals, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Thesis - Fragile Originals, 1938 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- National Maritime Union. Ledgers and Day Books (Box 36)
  - 14 Day 500D Book, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Book with folder of missing pages
  - 13 Book of Receipts, 1934 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - 12 Composition Book Property of JLD and JC Hall, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    Folder with registration forms and book
  - 11 EGSA Day Ledger, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - 10 Tanker Strike Donation Record (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - 9 National Order Book No. 1597, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - 8 Receipts, 1937-1939 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    Books
  - 7 Journal J-999, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - 6 Day Book D-999, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Folder with misc. receipts and book
  - 5 Day Book D-999 and Strike Fund Records, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    Folder with misc. papers and book
  - 4 Spring Composition Book #S707, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - 3 Journal J-999 and Papers, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    Book and folder with misc. papers
  - 2 Day Book - Clearances, 1937 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    Book and card
  - 1 Ledger (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Brittle - National Maritime Union, Sample Ballot (Box 37)
  - Sample Ballot (Original) Atlantic and Gulf Districts - National Maritime Union of America (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Preservation Copy and Original